{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","address":"1428 Gratiot Ave","zipcode":"48207","owner":"Greg Holm","licenseNumber":"078537","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"5/2/2017","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Permanently Closed","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E61000005826123871C254C0203168F8012C4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"40494","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","inspectionDate":"2017-10-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"129","pcount":"3","pfcount":"1","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"4","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40494","inspectionDate":"10/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \r\n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"intake air ducts","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Hood","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"inspectionid":"40494","inspectionDate":"10/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","violationCode":"4-501.112","violationDescription":"In a mechanical operation, the temperature of the fresh hot water SANITIZING rinse as it enters the manifold may not be more than 194 F, or less than 165 F for stationary rack machines or 180 F for all other machines to assure proper sanitizing of utensils. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Dish machine final rinse temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Above 194 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"At the Hot water sanitizing temperature","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"inspectionid":"40494","inspectionDate":"10/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Ice holding bin","location":"BAR ( FIRST FLOOR)","subLocation":"At the AIR GAP","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"inspectionid":"40494","inspectionDate":"10/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"juncture","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Coved molding","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."},{"inspectionid":"40494","inspectionDate":"10/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","violationCode":"4-501.12","violationDescription":"Surfaces such as cutting blocks and boards that are subject to scratching and scoring shall be resurfaced if they can no longer be effectively cleaned and SANITIZED, or discarded if they are not capable of being resurfaced.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Cutting surface(s)","subItem":"cutting board(s)","problemDescription":"With deep cuts/grooves","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Cutting board(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to provide smooth cutting surface."},{"inspectionid":"40494","inspectionDate":"10/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"BAR COOLER","subLocation":"At the COLD HOLDING TEMPERATURES","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"40494","inspectionDate":"10/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \r\n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\r\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\r\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"At the Past date food","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."}]},{"inspectionid":"38327","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","inspectionDate":"2017-03-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"129","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38327","inspectionDate":"3/21/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","violationCode":"4-501.12","violationDescription":"Surfaces such as cutting blocks and boards that are subject to scratching and scoring shall be resurfaced if they can no longer be effectively cleaned and SANITIZED, or discarded if they are not capable of being resurfaced.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Cutting surface(s)","subItem":"cutting board(s) at prep cooler","problemDescription":"With deep cuts/grooves","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Cutting board(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to provide smooth cutting surface."},{"inspectionid":"38327","inspectionDate":"3/21/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Open seams","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Coved molding","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"38327","inspectionDate":"3/21/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \r\n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\r\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\r\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"At the DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"38327","inspectionDate":"3/21/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"At the Hand washing signage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"}]},{"inspectionid":"36593","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","inspectionDate":"2016-09-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"121","pcount":"0","pfcount":"2","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36593","inspectionDate":"9/27/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"36593","inspectionDate":"9/27/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate sanitary hand drying aids/devices."},{"inspectionid":"36593","inspectionDate":"9/27/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4461","name":"Antietam","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4461"}}